♪ La-la-la la-la-la la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 啦-啦-啦 啦-啦-啦 ♪ 啦-啦-啦-啦 ♪
[blows whistle]
[吹哨]
- All right! Puppet roll call!
- 好了！木偶点名！
Nicky!
Nicky！
- Here!
- 到！
- Ricky!
- Ricky！
- Present!
- 在！
- Dicky!
- Dicky！
- How's it going?
- 怎么样？
[Dawn] All right, everyone.
[Dawn] 好了，各位。
Welcome to the opening day of puppet season.
欢迎来到木偶季的开幕日。
Now, I don't know about you, but I am sick
现在，我不知道你们怎么想，但我已经厌倦了每年在学校才艺表演中屈居第二。
of coming in second place at the school talent show every year.
我也是。
- Me too. - I hate losing to Pete Tibbals.
- 我也是。 - 我讨厌输给皮特·蒂巴尔斯。
Me too.
我也是。
Just because Pete Tibbals
就因为皮特·蒂巴尔斯
can fit his whole fist in his mouth.
能把他的整个拳头放进嘴里。
How is that a talent?
那算什么才艺？
I mean, anyone can.
我是说，任何人都可以。
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
Wow. Tibbals got skills.
哇，Tibbals有本事。
I think we all agree,
我想我们都同意，
we hate losing to Pete Tibbals.
我们都不想输给Pete Tibbals。
[all] Tibbals.
Tibbals。
But I've got some good news.
但我有个好消息。
His hands grew over the summer.
他夏天手长大了。
And he got braces!
还戴了牙套！
So his hand doesn't fit?
所以他的手塞不进去了？
Like stuffing a bowling ball in a tube sock.
就像把保龄球塞进袜子里。
- Yes! That means we're gonna win!
对！这意味着我们要赢了！
Not so fast.
别急。
Guys, it doesn't matter who we're up against.
伙计们，不管我们面对的是谁。
The Pigs is a second-place show.
《小猪们》是第二名的节目。
That's why, this year, we should finally do...
所以，今年我们应该终于做...
Goldilocks and the Three Bears!
《金发姑娘和三只熊！》
But we've been perfecting The Pigs for three years.
但我们已经完善《小猪们》三年了。
Why would we change now? This is our year.
我们为什么要现在改变？今年是我们的年。
I agree, but I think we should do something fresh
我同意，但我认为我们应该做一些新鲜的东西
that'll push us over the top.
这会让我们脱颖而出。
Guys, I just want us to win.
伙计们，我只希望我们能赢。
So do we. We just have to agree to agree.
我们也是这么想的。我们只需要达成共识。
But I disagree.
但我不同意。
Well, there's your problem.
好吧，这就是你的问题。
Look, there's an easy way to settle this.
听着，有个简单的方法来解决这个问题。
All in favor of doing The Three Little Pigs again?
所有赞成再次表演《三只小猪》的人？
It's "quad-nanimous."
这是“全票通过”。
Uh, it's only "quad-nanimous" if all four of us agree.
呃，只有我们四个人都同意才算是“全票通过”。
What does it matter?
这有什么关系？
- It matters 'cause you're not listening to me.
这很重要，因为你没有听我的。
Every year, I say we should do something different,
每年我都提议我们应该做些不同的，
and every year, you vote against me,
而每年，你都投票反对我，
and every year, we come in second.
而每年，我们都屈居第二。
What's the point of even voting?
投票还有什么意义？
She's right.
她说得对。
Voting's a waste of time.
投票纯粹是浪费时间。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
All in favor of getting rid of the vote
赞成取消投票
and always doing The Three Little Pigs?
并永远做《三只小猪》的人？
It's settled. "Boy-jority" rules.
就这么定了。“男孩多数”规则。
Oh, wait.
哦，等等。
What's that I hear?
我听到什么了？
Is that the second-place train?
那是第二名的火车吗？
[mimics train chugging] Second-second,
[模仿火车行驶声] 第二-第二，
second-second, second-second, second-second, second-second!
第二-第二，第二-第二，第二-第二，第二-第二！
[mimics train whistle] Lose! Lose!
[模仿火车汽笛声] 输！输！
[Tom gasps]
[汤姆倒吸一口气]
Is it puppet season already?
已经是木偶季节了吗？
Oh!
哦！
Old Alice looks better than ever.
老爱丽丝看起来比以往任何时候都好。
Tom, I know you love "Alice,"
汤姆，我知道你喜欢《爱丽丝》，
but you have to admit, she's seen better days.
但你必须承认，她已经过了巅峰时期。
It's true Alice is a puppet theater of a certain age,
确实，Alice是一个有一定历史的木偶剧院，
but she's seen me through a lot, Anne.
但她陪伴我经历了许多，Anne。
She's the stage upon which the next generation
她是下一代Harper木偶师磨练技艺的舞台。
of Harper puppeteers have honed their craft.
她是这一切的基石——
She's the very foundation of--
哇。
Whoa.
面对现实吧，Tom。
Face it, Tom.
Alice已经完成了她的最后一次木偶表演。
Alice has put on her last puppet show.
那么，我们为什么不问问孩子们呢？
Well, why don't we just ask the kids?
你们喜欢老Alice，对吧？
You love old Alice, right?
你们喜欢老爱丽丝，对吧？
- Yeah! - Absolutely.
- 是的！ - 绝对喜欢。
- Love her. - See? The kids understand.
- 爱她。 - 看吧？孩子们明白的。
That's because they haven't seen this.
那是因为他们还没见过这个。
[boys oohing]
[男孩们发出惊叹声]
It has twice the space and a padded floor
这里空间是原来的两倍，还有软垫地板
so your knees don't get sore.
这样你们的膝盖就不会痛了。
Oh, nice try, Anne, but my kids would never replace
哦，安妮，尝试不错，但我的孩子们绝不会
old, reliable Alice.
替换掉可靠的老爱丽丝。
- Yeah, we would. - Totally.
- 不，我们会。 - 绝对会。
She's out.
她出局了。
Dawn, you don't want to get rid of old Alice, right?
道恩，你不想放弃老爱丽丝，对吧？
It doesn't matter what puppet theater we use
无论我们使用哪个木偶剧场，
if we put the same lame, second-place show in it.
如果我们上演的是同样平庸、第二名的表演。
This is so amazing!
这太棒了！
So much better than Alice.
比爱丽丝好多了。
What are we gonna name her?
我们要给她起什么名字？
This is one heck of a start to puppet season!
这是木偶季的一个绝佳开始！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[rhythmic clapping] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Na, na-na ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, hey ♪
♪ Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦-哦，哦-哦 ♪
[sighs] Listen.
听着。
You guys were right.
你们说得对。
We should definitely do The Three Little Pigs again.
我们确实应该再演《三只小猪》。
But what if we spiced it up a little and did something crazy,
但如果我们稍微加点料，做点疯狂的事，
like, I don't know... gave the wolf golden locks?
比如说，我不知道...给狼加上金色的头发？
Interesting.
有意思。
I'm listening.
我在听。
Then she could-- I'm just spit-balling here--
然后她可以——我只是随便说说——
go into the pigs' house and sample their food,
进入小猪的房子，品尝他们的食物，
furnishings, and bedding.
家具和床上用品。
That could work!
这可能行得通！
And make the pigs bears.
然后把猪变成熊。
Let's vote on it.
我们来投票决定吧。
All in favor of telling Dawn
所有赞成告诉Dawn
she's not fooling us and the only way to win
她骗不了我们，唯一能赢的方法
is sticking with The Three Little Pigs?
是坚持《三只小猪》吗？
I thought you weren't voting anymore.
我以为你不再投票了。
All in favor of reinstating the vote so we can vote Dawn down?
所有赞成恢复投票以便我们可以否决Dawn的？
Sorry, Dawn.
对不起，Dawn。
You lose now, but we're all gonna win later.
你现在输了，但我们大家以后都会赢的。
Ooh, don't forget,
哦，别忘了，
we're rehearsing right after school.
我们放学后马上就要排练。
And you won't be needing this. Hmm.
而且你不会需要这个的。嗯。
- Hey, Dawn. - Hey, Mack.
- 嘿，Dawn。 - 嘿，Mack。
So, listen, I was wondering if maybe you wanted
所以，听着，我在想你放学后要不要一起踢球？
to kick the ball around after school?
我不能。我实际上有训练。
I can't. I actually have practice.
[Dicky] 看我！我是Dawn！
[Dicky] Look at me! I'm Dawn!
[Ricky] 小金发姑娘！
[Ricky] Little Goldilocks!
把假发给我！
Give me the wig!
It's my turn to play second place.
轮到我扮演第二名了。
Nothing.
没什么。
I have nothing to practice after school.
放学后我没什么可练习的。
I'd love to hang out.
我很想一起玩。
Great. See you then.
太好了。到时候见。
[Nicky] Goldilocks is the worst!
[Nicky] 金发姑娘最差劲了！
[as puppet] Oh, no, you didn't!
[模仿木偶] 哦，不，你没做到！
Oh, yes, I did!
哦，是的，我做到了！
Hmm!
哼！
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na-na na na na, hey ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐，嘿 ♪
- [gasps] Ooh!
- [吸气] 哦！
I think I see the puppet theater delivery guy.
我想我看到木偶剧场的送货员了。
You know, Anne...
你知道，安妮...
it's easy to be tempted by a shiny, new puppet theater.
被一个闪亮的新木偶剧场吸引很容易。
But you're making a mistake turning your back on old Alice.
但你转身离开老爱丽丝是个错误。
Yeah! They don't make 'em like they used to.
是啊！他们不再像以前那样制作了。
That's removable.
那是可以拆卸的。
See? I can't have that happen up on stage.
看？我不能让这种事在舞台上发生。
You can't have that happen?
你不能让那种事发生？
I mean the kids.
我是说那些孩子们。
It would be really embarrassing for me--them!
那对我——他们来说真的很尴尬！
I would never hear the end of it--they!
我永远也听不到尽头——他们！
[sighs]
叹气
Call me crazy, but I think there's something else going on here.
叫我疯子吧，但我觉得这里还有别的事情。
Fine, Tom! It's embarrassing.
好吧，汤姆！是尴尬。
I see the other parents pointing.
我看到其他家长在指指点点。
I hear them whispering, "Look at her, she's pathetic."
我听到他们在窃窃私语，'看她，她真可怜。'
[gasps] They don't say that about you.
惊讶声 他们不会那样说你。
Not about me. About Alice.
不是说我，是说Alice。
[gasps] They may say that about you,
他们可能会那么说你，
but they do not say that about Alice!
但他们不会那么说Alice！
Oh, yes, they do, Tom.
哦，不，他们会的，Tom。
But not this year.
但不是今年。
The new puppet theater is gonna change all that.
新的木偶剧场将会改变这一切。
I'll show them.
我会让他们看到的。
So you're saying you care more about what other people think
所以你是说你更在乎别人怎么想
than about my feelings?
而不是我的感受？
[doorbell rings]
门铃响了。
I need to answer that, Tom.
我得去应门，汤姆。
You're darn right you do!
你当然得去！
I meant the door.
我是说去开门。
Oh, I guess I have my answer.
哦，我想我知道答案了。
[Ricky] Where have you been?
[瑞奇]你去哪儿了？
You've missed most of rehearsal!
你错过了大部分排练！
Oh, did I? Sorry.
哦，是吗？对不起。
Mack and I were hanging out and I guess I lost track of time.
麦克和我一直在闲逛，我猜我没注意时间。
Well, I hope your fingers are warm,
好吧，希望你的手指是暖和的，
'cause we're jumping right in.
因为我们马上就要开始了。
Okay, we'll pick it up with the wolf at the door.
好的，我们从狼来到门口的地方开始。
[as puppet] Not by the hairs of my chinny-chin-chin!
【玩偶音】休想拔下我下巴上的一根毛！
[half-hearted] Huff, puff, blow your house down.
【敷衍地】呼、呼，吹倒你的房子。
[blows raspberry]
【发出噗的声音】
Oh, well, good enough for second place.
哦，好吧，足够拿第二名了。
- See ya. - Where you going?
- 再见。- 你去哪儿？
Uh, that's all the rehearsal I need,
呃，这是我需要的所有排练，
so I'm gonna continue to skip rehearsal every day
所以我会继续每天翘掉排练
to hang out with Mack.
去和麦克试试看。
Unless you want to rehearse something
除非你想排练一些
that actually has a chance of winning.
实际上有机会获胜的。
Until then, blow your own house down.
在那之前，自己把自己的房子吹倒吧。
If she keeps this up, we're no longer the front-runners.
如果她继续这样下去，我们就不再是领先者了。
We could lose to the juggling Branzinos!
我们可能会输给那些玩杂耍的布兰齐诺鱼！
You shut your puppet hole!
你闭上你的木偶嘴！
We will not get second place again.
我们不会再拿第二名了。
And we will not let Dawn sink this ship.
我们不会让Dawn搞砸这一切。
We need to keep her focused on what's important: us.
我们需要让她专注于重要的事情：我们。
Yeah, we need to get rid of Dawn's little distraction.
是的，我们需要消除Dawn的小干扰。
I think it's about time we pay Mack a little visit.
我想是时候我们去拜访一下Mack了。
But we need to be smart about it.
但我们必须聪明行事。
No one can know it's us.
不能让任何人知道是我们。
Hey, eyelashes.
嘿，眼睫毛。
Whoa...whoa...whoa!
哇...哇...哇！
Hey. Awesome puppets.
嘿。很棒的木偶。
We're not here to chitchat, punk.
我们不是来闲聊的，小子。
What are you guys doing?
你们在干什么？
Don't look at them.
别看他们。
This is between us.
这是我们之间的事。
Word on the street is you have a thing
街上传言说你有个习惯，
for interrupting puppet practice.
专门打断木偶练习的。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
We're talking about you making us
我们在说你让我们
have to postpone puppet practice,
不得不推迟木偶练习，
you pretty little pepper pot!
你这个可爱的小多嘴！
What's a pepper pot?
什么是多嘴？
Somebody who asks too many questions!
就是问太多问题的人！
Dawn was late yesterday...
昨天黎明迟到了...
because of you, pal!
都是因为你，伙计！
Guys, I'm sorry. I had no idea.
伙计们，对不起。我完全不知道。
I told you not to look at them!
我告诉过你不要看他们！
All right, bub, here's how it's gonna be!
好吧，小子，事情会这样发展！
You cancel your plans with Dawn this afternoon,
你取消今天下午和Dawn的计划，
or we're gonna cancel you.
否则我们会取消你。
This is our year, and we're not gonna let you,
这是我们的一年，我们不会让你，
or your awesome eyelashes, get in the way of us
或是你的超棒睫毛，妨碍我们
winning that talent show!
赢得那个才艺表演！
Look, I don't want any trouble.
听着，我不想惹麻烦。
I'll stay away from Dawn.
我会远离Dawn。
Glad you see things our way.
很高兴你看到我们的方式。
Our work here is done, boys.
我们的任务完成了，伙计们。
Let's roll.
我们出发吧。
[boys imitating engines revving]
[男孩们模仿引擎轰鸣声]
Okay, yeah, I just need to find the Flugenfleegan
好的，是的，我只需要找到Flugenfleegan
and put it in the Flechenstichen.
然后把它放进Flechtenstichen。
You know what's great theater?
你知道什么才是精彩的戏剧吗？
Watching you try to build a theater.
看你尝试建造一个剧院。
What? I just need to get this peg
什么？我只需要把这个钉子
into this ridiculously tiny hooollleee.
放进这个荒谬的小洞里。
Ugh!
呃！
Come on. Okay.
来吧。好吧。
I-will-not-be- humiliated--oh!
我-不-会被-羞辱--哦！
Ohh!
哦！
You know, Anne, when I built Alice.
你知道吗，安妮，当我建造爱丽丝的时候。
there wasn't any shouting or shoe hammering.
没有喊叫也没有用鞋子敲打。
- Hmph! - Hmm.
- 哼！ - 嗯。
It was easy. Ooh.
那很容易。哦。
Because I built her for the right reasons.
因为我为了正确的理由建造她。
Not to quiet the whispers or stop the pointing,
不是为了平息流言蜚语或停止指指点点，
but to give the puppets a place to shine
而是为了让木偶们有个发光的地方
and tell their stories.
并讲述他们的故事。
Tom...
汤姆...
You are this close to getting Schlugenviel
你差点就要在斯洛根博施里得到施卢根维尔了。
in your Sloggenbosch.
一、二，一、二——
[both] And one, and two, and one, and two--
我听说三只小猪突然来了一场即兴的木偶聚会，还有一个漂亮的胡椒罐。
So I hear three little piggies popped in
至少我们的木偶没有吐口水。
for an impromptu puppet powwow with a pretty pepper pot.
下次，离麦克远点。
At least our puppets didn't spit.
我们只和麦克交谈，因为我们如果不来练习就永远赢不了
Next time, stay away from Mack.
嗯，我宁愿和麦克一起玩
We only talked to Mack because we're never gonna win
如果我们不参加练习，就永远拿不到第一名。
first place if you don't show up to practice.
如果你不参加练习，我们永远拿不到第一名。
Well, I'd rather hang out with Mack
好吧，我宁愿和Mack一起玩，
than practice some dumb old play
也不愿练习那个愚蠢的老剧，
that's not gonna win us first place.
那个剧不会让我们赢得第一名。
You know what? Mack's not the problem.
你知道吗？问题不在Mack。
You are, Dawn.
是你，Dawn。
Oh, I'm the problem? Okay, then fine.
哦，我是问题？好吧，那就好。
Problem solved. I quit.
问题解决了。我退出。
[all] What?
什么？
- Have fun coming in last.
祝你们最后一名玩得开心。
You don't get to tell us what to do!
你没资格命令我们！
Hey, Dad, what's wrong?
嘿，爸爸，怎么了？
Nothing.
没事。
Just getting some ice for my Sloggenbosch.
只是去拿点冰给我的Sloggenbosch。
Whew.
呼。
♪ [whistling] ♪
♪ [吹口哨] ♪
The Branzino Sisters smell blood.
Branzino姐妹嗅到了血腥味。
They think now that Dawn's off our team, we're weak.
她们认为既然Dawn离开了我们的团队，我们就变弱了。
Are we?
我们真的变弱了吗？
Relax, we're gonna be fine.
放松，我们会没事的。
Dawn's gonna come crawling back to us.
Dawn会爬回来找我们的。
Look, here she comes now.
看，她现在来了。
Dawn, let us save you the trouble
Dawn，让我们省去你爬回来的麻烦。
of crawling back to us. Yes, we'll take you back.
是的，我们会接受你回来。
I'm not crawling back to you.
我不会爬回来找你们。
I was looking for this...
我一直在找这个……
Which goes with this.
它和这个搭配。
[all] A puppet?
所有人：一个木偶？
Which goes with this.
它和这个搭配。
[all] Mack?
所有人：Mack？
My new partner for my own puppet show.
我的新搭档，为我的木偶戏准备的。
Show them your puppet, Mack.
麦克，给他们看看你的木偶。
[all] Mack's puppet?
麦克的木偶？
That's a bear, as in Goldilocks and the three of them.
那是一只熊，就像《金发姑娘和三只熊》里的那样。
No hard feelings here, guys.
这里没有恶意，伙计们。
Yeah, like we're afraid of a sock puppet.
是啊，好像我们会怕一个袜子木偶似的。
[laughs]
[笑]
Mack, show 'em what you got.
麦克，给他们看看你的本事。
This porridge is too hot.
这粥太烫了。
This porridge is too cold.
这粥太冷了。
This one is just right. Hmm.
这个正好。嗯。
How did he do that?
他是怎么做到的？
He went to puppet camp.
他去了木偶营。
[gasps]
（吸气声）
And it was sleep away.
而且是过夜的那种。
[all gasp]
（所有人吸气）
Good luck at the talent show. Hmm.
祝你在才艺表演好运。嗯。
Two hands?
两只手？
- Three puppets? - It's over!
- 三个木偶？ - 完了！
It's not over. We can still win without Dawn.
还没完。没有Dawn我们也能赢。
Yes we can.
是的，我们可以。
We just gotta get Mack.
我们只需要搞定麦基。
We can't get Mack. Dawn got Mack.
我们搞不定麦基，道恩搞定了麦基。
Well, if we get Dawn back, Mack'll come with her.
好吧，如果我们把道恩找回来，麦基就会跟着她一起来。
We're not getting either of them.
我们哪一个都找不回来。
We just need to find someone who's better than Dawn.
我们只需要找到比道恩更厉害的人。
Oh, I know somebody.
哦，我知道一个人。
- Who? - Mack.
- 谁？- 麦基。
I'm out.
我退出。
♪ Uh, uh, oh Hey, uh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ 呃，呃，哦 嘿，呃，哦-哦-哦-哦 ♪
So tell me why you think you'd be right
for the role of the Big Bad Wolf.
[low voice] Well, I'm big and I'm bad,
and I've been told I have wolf breath.
Okay.
Let's take it from, "Not by the hair
of my chinny-chin-chin." And...puppet.
Then I'll huff and I'll puff
and I'll blow your house down!
- [coughs] - Oh.
She does have wolf breath.
她的确有狼的气息。
Next.
下一个。
And I'll huff and I'll puff
我会呼气和吹气
and I'll blow your house down.
然后吹倒你的房子！
[coughs]
咳！
Next!
下一个！
And I'll huff and I'll puff
我会呼气和吹气
and I'll blow your house down!
然后吹倒你的房子！
[applause]
（掌声）
- Well done. - Very nice.
- 干得好。- 非常好。
We found our new wolf.
我们找到了我们的新狼。
Oh, I told you guys, I'm just here to pick you up.
哦，我告诉过你们，我只是来接你们的。
But please, you're perfect.
但请你们，你们太完美了。
I'm not even a student here.
我甚至不是这里的学生。
Oh, why don't you guys use Mack?
哦，你们为什么不找麦克呢？
I heard him in the hallway. He is a natural.
我在走廊里听到他了。他是个天生的。
He's not a natural! He went to camp!
他不是天生的！他去过训练营！
Okay, whoa, sorry. I'll meet you outside.
好吧，哇，对不起。外面见。
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
我来告诉你们我们要做什么。
I'm gonna put a pig on one hand, a wolf on the on the other,
我打算一手拿只猪，另一手拿只狼，
and go out there and puppet like no one else can.
然后出去表演，让所有人都惊叹。
Except maybe Mack.
除了可能的Mack。
Ricky's getting upset!
Ricky要生气了！
♪ La la la la la la la la ♪
♪啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦♪
[sighs]
[叹气]
And...done.
然后...完成了。
And...miss.
然后...失误了。
W-w-what part is a miss?
哪...哪部分失误了？
Oh, well, you know, just basically...this.
哦，你知道的，基本上就是...这个。
Just help me get it to the car.
帮我把它弄到车上。
Ugh.
呃。
Okay. Okay.
好吧，好吧。
Yup, yup, yup, yup.
对，对，对，对。
Hon, I don't think it's gonna--
亲爱的，我觉得它装不下——
It's gonna fit!
一定能装下！
The door's too small.
车门太小了。
Make it wider!
把它弄宽点！
I can't make it wider.
我没法把它弄宽。
Ugh! I'll do it myself!
呃！我自己来！
[grunting]
[咕哝声]
Okay, okay, okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Hon, hon, hon, hon, hon, hey, hey, listen, listen.
亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，亲爱的，嘿，嘿，听着，听着。
What?
什么？
Even if you could get it through the door,
即使你能把它弄进门，
is this what you want the world to see?
这是你想让世界看到的吗？
[panting]
[喘气声]
No.
不。
It's okay. It's okay.
没关系。没关系。
Then let's show those pointers and whisperers
那我们就展示那些指指点点和窃窃私语的人
something we can both be proud of.
这是我们都能引以为傲的东西。
No, Tom. Let's do it for the puppets...
不，汤姆。让我们为了那些木偶...
And their stories.
以及他们的故事。
That's my girl.
这才是我的女孩。
Oh!
哦！
♪ La la la la la la la la ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
[playing water-filled glasses]
[演奏装水的玻璃杯]
♪ ♪
I feel so pretty. We're crushing this!
我感觉如此美丽。我们做得太棒了！
♪ ♪
[applause]
Let's give it up for Indra and Oscar.
That was oddly moving.
- Well, well, well, if it isn't the three little piggies
who are gonna cry, "Wee, wee, wee,
all the way to second place."
Clever, but your snappy wordplay isn't gonna save you
once our puppet fists of fury hit the stage!
I don't need word play. I've got Mack.
He is really good.
Yes, we know! He's good!
是的，我们知道！他很棒！
- Puppets up next. Up next, puppets.
- 接下来是木偶表演。接下来，木偶。
- Okay, easy. [Anne] Ugh.
- 好的，轻松。[Anne] 呃。
- Easy. [Anne] Ugh!
- 轻松。[Anne] 呃！
- Easy. - Ugh! Easy for you.
- 轻松。- 呃！对你来说轻松。
I could use a little help.
我可能需要一点帮助。
No, you're doing great. Easy.
不，你做得很好。轻松。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- Easy. - [groaning]
- 轻松。- [呻吟]
[Tom] Easy.
[Tom] 轻松。
Where is your little golden boy, anyway?
话说回来，你的小金童在哪里？
He's here. He's just doing his special puppet warm-ups.
他在这里。他只是在进行他的特别木偶热身。
Well, you may have Mack,
好吧，你可能有麦克，
but we've got the best wolf that we've ever had.
但我们有我们迄今为止最好的狼。
Oh really?
哦，真的吗？
Yeah. He's huffy and puffy,
是的。他有点暴躁和气喘，
but in a good way.
但这是好事。
What's that supposed to mean?
那是什么意思？
You know what it means.
你知道那是什么意思。
I'm only huffy and puffy because you guys are blowhards!
我之所以暴躁和气喘，是因为你们这些家伙太能吹了！
Up next, The Three Little Pigs performed by the...
接下来，《三只小猪》由...
This is interesting... Harper Triplets.
这挺有意思的...哈珀三胞胎。
[all arguing]
[都在争吵]
Harper Triplets? You three little pigs!
哈珀三胞胎？你们这三只小猪！
[all gasp]
[都惊讶]
I've built my house of straw.
我用稻草建了我的房子。
It's not very sturdy, but I'll have lots of time to play.
虽然不太坚固，但我有很多时间可以玩耍。
Little Pig! Little Pig! Let me come in.
小猪！小猪！让我进去。
[scoffs] Nice wolf voice.
[嘲笑]狼的声音不错。
Not by the hair of my chinny-chin-chin.
绝不会让我的下巴毛被吹走。
Well then I'll huff...
好吧，那我要吹气了...
In a really good wolf voice--
用一个非常棒的狼的声音——
And I'll puff...
然后我要呼气...
Way better than the previous puffer--
比之前的呼气者好多了——
And I'll blow your house down!
然后我会把你的房子吹倒！
You call that puffing?
你那也叫呼气？
The previous wolf was way better.
之前的狼可比你强多了。
How would you know, Goldilocks?
你怎么知道的，金发姑娘？
You're not even in the right fairy tale.
你甚至不在正确的童话故事里。
What'evs, pig boy!
随便啦，猪小子！
Uh, what are they doing?
呃，他们在做什么？
Making a mockery of puppet season.
在嘲笑木偶季。
On the upside, everyone loves the new theater.
不过，好处是大家都喜欢新剧院。
This is just like Goldilocks,
这就像金发姑娘一样，
barging into a place she doesn't belong.
闯进一个不属于她的地方。
Breaking chairs, eating porridge,
弄坏椅子，吃掉粥，
and filling up the DVR with the shows
还用节目塞满DVR，
the bears don't want to watch.
那些熊不想看的节目。
I thought we were pigs.
我以为我们是猪。
Pigs, bears, brothers, doesn't matter!
猪也好，熊也好，兄弟也好，都不重要！
Living with you is impossible!
和你住在一起根本不可能！
Uh...and scene.
呃...幕落。
Let's give it up for the puppet stylings
让我们为哈珀家庭木偶剧团的精彩表演鼓掌。
of the Harper Family Players.
[掌声]
[applause] - Uh--
接下来，道恩和马克将带来更多的木偶乐趣，
Up next, Dawn and Mack with more puppet fun,
稍后，皮特·蒂博尔斯将尝试将保龄球塞进长袜里。
and later, Pete Tibbals will attempt
[瑞奇] 不，都是你的错！
to stuff a bowling ball in a tube sock.
你让我们太丢脸了！
[Ricky] No, your fault!
我希望你满意。
[Dicky] You totally embarrassed us!
[Dicky] 你完全让我们丢脸了！
[Nicky] I hope you're happy.
[Nicky] 我希望你感到高兴。
[all arguing]
[所有人争吵]
Stop it!
停下来！
What is this all about?
这到底是怎么回事？
[all] She/They started it!
[所有人] 是她/他们先开始的！
- Dawn, we're up.
- Dawn, 轮到我们了。
[all] Not now!
[所有人] 现在不行！
Whoa, what has gotten into you guys?
哇，你们这是怎么了？
Yeah, I thought you were working together.
是啊，我以为你们是在一起工作的。
If we were really working "together,"
如果我們真的在'合作',
they wouldn't always vote against me.
他們就不會總反對我。
We don't always vote against you.
我們並不是每次都反對你。
- I'm with Ricky. - Me too.
- 我支持Ricky。- 我也是。
See?
看到了嗎？
You don't even realize you're doing it.
你們甚至沒意識到自己在做什麼。
But we voted. It's fair.
但我們投票了，這很公平。
It may be fair, but it's not right.
或許公平，但不正確。
You know what's not right?
你知道什麼不正確嗎？
Not getting your way and bailing on us.
達不成自己的意願就拋棄我們。
And then replacing us with Mack.
然后还用Mack取代了我们。
At least he listens to me.
至少他会听我的。
And he's scary good at puppets.
而且他在操纵木偶方面非常厉害。
Yes, we know he's good.
是的，我们知道他很厉害。
But it's not about Mack. You just made us mad.
但这不是关于Mack的问题。你只是让我们生气了。
We were upset because we knew without you,
我们感到沮丧是因为我们知道没有你，
we had no chance of winning.
我们没有赢的机会。
And I knew I couldn't win without you either.
而且我知道没有你我也赢不了。
I just wanted to be heard.
我只是想被听到。
Well, then maybe we should try and be better listeners.
那么，也许我们应该尝试成为更好的倾听者。
All in favor of being better listeners?
赞成成为更好的倾听者吗？
It's quad-nanimous.
全票通过。
Oh, we're so proud of you. Mwah.
哦，我们为你感到骄傲。亲一个。
- Truth is, you never had a shot anyway.
- 事实上，你本来就没有机会。
I mean, look at that kid.
我是说，看看那个孩子。
[Mack] ♪ Row row row your boat ♪
[Mack] ♪ 划呀划你的船 ♪
- ♪ Gently down the stream ♪ - ♪ Row row row your boat ♪
♪ 轻轻地顺流而下 ♪ - ♪ 划呀划你的船 ♪
- ♪ Merrily, merrily... ♪ - ♪ Row row row your boat ♪
♪ 快乐地，快乐地... ♪ - ♪ 划呀划你的船 ♪
- ♪ Merrily, merrily... ♪ - ♪ Life is but a dream ♪
♪ 快乐地，快乐地... ♪ - ♪ 生活不过是一场梦 ♪
- ♪ Row row row your boat ♪ - ♪ Life is but a dream ♪
♪ 划呀划你的船 ♪ - ♪ 生活不过是一场梦 ♪
Man, that must be one heck of a camp.
伙计，那一定是个非常棒的营地。
- ♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
- [发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
- ♪